https://medsafetyofficer.org/content/medication-safety-officers-society-privacy-policy

Privacy Statement for www.medsafetyofficer.org
The Medication Safety Officers Society (MSOS) has created this statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. This statement will help you understand how your personally identifiable information is collected and how that information may be shared. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for www.medsafetyofficer.org.
NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES TO PRIVACY STATEMENT
Users can find out about changes in this privacy statement by visiting this page. This statement was last revised on May 7, 2014. We encourage users to read this statement thoroughly and use it as a point of reference for the future.
COOKIES
Our site uses cookies to keep track of your online shopping cart. The shopping cart may not perform correctly if the cookies option is turned off in the browser settings. The MSOS web site uses cookies to restrict access to some content. MSOS members who elect to browse the site with the cookies option turned off will not be able to access restricted content.
LOG FILES
Browser type, IP address, access time, and files accessed are collected in log files. MSOS uses this information to analyze traffic on the site and then discards the log files. Aggregate information generated from the log files is sometimes shared with advertisers.
PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION
The site collects personally identifiable information at the following locations: MSOS Membership, Change of Personal Information Form for MSOS Members, MSOS Shopping Cart, and Listserv sign-up. The information collected may include name, title, home address, business address, practice demographics, e-mail, and credit card number (when a purchase is made). We use customer contact information from the forms to send orders, email news services, newsletters, and event announcements. A credit card processing company is used to process credit card transactions. The credit card information is used only for billing purposes. The nonfinancial information we collect is sometimes shared with other reputable organizations to help them contact consumers for marketing purposes. Users may choose to decline receiving future mailings; please see the "Opting Out" section below. Aggregated demographic information may also be compiled and shared, but does not identify the individual user.
LINKS
This site contains links to other sites. MSOS is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other Web sites. Please read the privacy statements of the sites to which we link as their privacy practices may differ from www.medsafetyofficer.org.
SURVEY INFORMATION
Personally identifiable information is optional in our online surveys and would be used only to contact somebody to clarify an answer. Demographic and profile data that are collected are analyzed and shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.
E-MAIL
Throughout this site, users are provided the opportunity to communicate with MSOS via e-mail. We read every message and try to reply promptly to every one. This information is used to reply directly to your questions or comments. MSOS does not sell or rent email address information of our customers/members.
PUBLIC FORUMS, BLOGS, AND LISTSERV
This site makes discussion threads and listserv subscriptions available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information included in internet search engine results. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal information. These forums are moderated and inappropriate messages will be removed.
OPTING OUT
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt out of receiving communications from MSOS and any third parties at the point where the information is submitted.
Choosing to opt out of emails currently means you will NOT receive ANY email from MSOS (including the listserv). Likewise, opting out of emails and mailings means you will receive no announcements about upcoming meetings or product announcements and promotions.
CHANGING INFORMATION
Users have the ability to change information previously provided such as name, address, telephone, and e-mail address. All changes must be made in the user controlled change request area.
SECURITY
Maintaining the integrity of data collected at www.medsafetyofficer.org is of utmost importance to MSOS. Credit card information is transmitted in encrypted form. Personally identifiable information is stored behind password protection.
QUESTIONS
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your use of this Web site, please contact the MSOS Web team:
To prevent automated spam submissions leave this field empty.
